Everybody has looked in the mirror at some point in their lives and thought they could do with a smaller nose or fewer wrinkles.
每个人在生活中的某个时刻都曾照过镜子，并想过自己如果能有个更小的鼻子或更少的皱纹就好了。
Almost 10 million operations were performed in 2014, according to the International Society of Aesthetic Plastic Surgery.
根据国际美容整形外科学会的数据，2014年进行了近1000万例整形手术。
Eyelid surgery topped the list of the five most popular procedures, which included breast augmentation and rhinoplasty.
在五种最受欢迎的手术中，眼睑（眼皮）手术位居榜首，其他还包括隆胸和鼻整形术。
We hear a lot about cosmetic surgery these days.
如今我们经常听到关于整容手术的消息。
But what many people may not realise is that reconstructing someone's face has an ancient past.
但许多人可能没有意识到，面部重塑手术有着悠久的历史。
There are reports of treatments to restore a broken nose in ancient Egyptian documents.
古埃及文献中就有关于修复鼻梁断裂的治疗方法的记载。
Considering that safe anaesthetics and antibiotics were only discovered in the 19th and 20th centuries, it was a truly painful and risky business to go under the knife in the past.
考虑到安全的麻醉剂和抗生素直到19世纪和20世纪才被发现，过去接受手术是一件极其痛苦且危险的事情。
But as far back as the mid-15th century nose jobs were carried out using skin taken from the upper arm.
但早在15世纪中叶，鼻部整形手术就已经开始使用从上臂取下的皮肤。
Plastic surgery went through a revolution during World War One.
第一次世界大战期间，整形手术经历了一场革命。
The trenches protected the soldiers' bodies, but many who stuck their heads up were exposed to explosions.
战壕保护了士兵的身体，但许多探出头的人却暴露在爆炸中。
New techniques were developed by Harold Gillies who ran a ward at the Cambridge Military Hospital in Britain, and later a whole hospital dedicated to helping disfigured soldiers.
哈罗德·吉尔斯开发了许多新技术，他在英国剑桥军事医院管理一个病房，后来开设了一整家医院，致力于帮助毁容的士兵。
Many wounded men at that time couldn't stand looking at their own faces.
当时许多受伤的士兵无法忍受看到自己的脸。
There were no mirrors in the hospital.
医院里没有镜子。
In parks near the hospital, some benches were painted blue to signal to patients with facial injuries that they could sit there.
在医院附近的公园里，一些长椅被涂成蓝色，以向面部受伤的患者示意他们可以坐在那里。
And it was a way of telling local residents to prepare for the shock of seeing someone with a disfigured face.
这也是告诉当地居民，让看到毁容的人做好心理准备。
Plastic surgery has come a long way since then.
从那时起，整形手术已经取得了长足的进步。
It reconstructs what does need reconstructing but it also makes people with no particular problems feel more confident.
它不仅重塑了需要修复的部位，也让那些没有特别问题的人感到更加自信。
Bigger breasts?
隆胸？
Straight nose?
笔直的鼻梁？
Facelift?
面部拉皮？
In many cases, cosmetic surgery isn't a necessity at all, just a choice.
在许多情况下，美容手术根本不是必需品，而只是一种选择。
But when done properly by capable doctors on patients who have a realistic goal, it's believed that plastic surgery can heal psychological wounds almost as much as physical ones.
但如果由有能力的医生为有现实目标的患者进行手术，人们相信整形手术可以同样有效地治愈心理创伤和身体创伤。